Mireya Garza

Houston, TX | mire.garza98@gmail.com

Summary

I am a senior at the University of Houston-Clear Lake with a passion for computer science and graphic design. Through my college career I have received the opportunity to learn how to collaborate with others and develop crucial technical skills. My work experience has allowed me to excel in problem solving, team collaboration, and leadership skills. I believe my skills and enthusiasm in this field will prove very useful in a collaborative and innovative environment.

Skills

Design: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe illustrator, Adobe After effects, Adobe premiere pro CC **Web Development:** miregarza.github.io, uhclspiritsquad.github.io and katnapper98.github.io

Programming Languages: Java, Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL

Languages: Fluent Spanish

Work Experience

Student Mentor

University of Houston-Clear Lake- Houston, TX

(January 2017 - Present)

- Help students become familiar with topics discussed in class
- Plan and organize workshop events
- Help students become familiar with University resources

Graphic Designer

Teatrx- Houston, TX

(June 2018 – September 2018)

- Conceptualize and design original logos
- Conceptualize and express company culture into logo design
- Meet and collaborate with company executives on designs concepts

Intern

Tietronix Software

(January 2018 - June 2018)

- Front-end development
- Web application testing

Swim instructor

Lobo Gymnastics- Houston, TX

(June 2016 - August 2016)

- Create lesson plans for different classes and age groups
- discipline and keep students engaged in class
- lifeguard duty

Volunteer Experience

Teal Run Swim Team- Houston, TX

(June 2015 to August 2015)

- Help children with swimming instruction
- Give friendly and instructional attention to various children
- Help out at swim events

Houston Humane Society- Houston, TX

(May 2014 to August 2014)

- Oversee adoptions and well-being of animals
- Cleaned and fed pens
- Helped customers interested in adopting

Education

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

University of Houston-Clear Lake (august 2015 - Present) GPA: 3.184